September 12, 2014
A building at The SCOAN collapses after a strange aircraft flies low,
multiple times over it before disappearing.
SCOAN visitors capture the strange aircraft on their cameras at the entrance of the building.
A SOCAN visitors photo - a strange aircraft flies low over a building at The SCOAN.
This is the enlarged view of the photograph that was taken.
It reveals the close proximity at which the strange aircraft flew over the building,
shortly before its collapse.
Security footage, September 12, 2014.
A strange aircraft flies low over a building at The SCOAN multiple times
before the incident and after the incident, the strange aircraft does not return.
September 12, 2014.
Take note of the upper left hand corner of the screen.
A strange aircraft flies over the building at The SCOAN before the incident at 11:30 AM.
Thirteen minutes later, the strange aircraft flies low over the building before the incident at 11:43 AM.
Just two minutes later, the strange aircraft returns
and flies lower over the building before the incident at 11:45 AM.
Nine minutes later, the strange aircraft returns
and again flies low over the building before the incident at 11:54 AM.
This is the moment of the incident.
After the incident, the strange aircraft does not return.
CCTV Footage - Camera 6, September 12, 2014.
The incident from another angle.
Footage from another CCTV camera, positioned facing the end of the building.
It reveals the incident from another closer angle.
Take note of the building in the upper right hand corner of the screen.
From this angle, you can see clearly the precise moment of the incident.
THE MOMENT OF THE INCIDENT
Take note of the top of the screen.
As the CCTV footage plays in slow motion, it reveals exactly what happened to the building,
frame by frame during the incident.
Look again to what happens to the building during the exact moments of the incident
as the CCTV camera continues to reveal in slow motion each moment of the incident.
THE MOMENT OF THE INCIDENT
This is the moment of the incident.
Scene of the demolished building.
Floors piled on top of each other.
We at Emmanuel TV and The Synagogue Church Of All Nations
express our deepest condolences to the government of Nigeria,
the government of South Africa, and the governments of other affected nations,
most especially the families, friends, and loved ones of the precious souls
who lost their lives in the tragic incident which occurred on Friday, September 12, 2014.
May Almighty God console all and give courage and strength to bear the grievous losses.
We pray that God's presence in our hearts and lives would more than supply their absence.
Death to a believer is his release from the imprisonment of this world
and his departure to the enjoyment of another world.
Those who are born from above long to be there.
Those who lost their lives in the incident died not in vain but as martyrs of the Kingdom of God.
As the Psalmist reflects, "Precious in the sight of the Lord is the death of His saints" (Psalm 116:15).
God's everlasting promise is to comfort all who mourn, provide for those who grieve,
to bestow on them a crown of beauty for ashes, the oil of joy for mourning
and a garment of praise for a spirit of despair (Isaiah 61:3).
Trouble may endure for the night but joy comes in the morning!
To all we greet you: Good Morning!
Emmanuel!
God is with us!
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV - Changing lives, Changing nations, and Changing the world.
RV: Mel Flowers 13/04/2019